worldvitalrecords.com 2014-02-14

# World Vital Records - Genealogy Privacy Policy

Last updated December 28, 2007 

Thank you for placing your trust in us and in our continued work to bring you global information as we steadily acquire, process and post records to our site. We value this trust and your privacy as you grow with us. We, at WorldVitalRecords.com, won't rent, sell or trade your personal information or email address to any third party. We use your information only for your subscription and/or the newsletter services as described here in our Privacy Policy. We regard the protection of your privacy as an important part of our business.

You can unsubscribe for any reason at any time to the Web site or the newsletter. If you ever have a problem with your subscription to the Web site or the newsletter, feel free to contact our Customer Service personnel via our contact form. If you wish to cancel your subscription to World Vital Records, please contact us by phone at 1-888-377-0588 between the hours of 7-5 p.m. (Mountain Standard Time). If you live outside the United States, please dial the international country code for your country, and then dial 1-801-377-0588.

If you are a subscriber to our services, it is your responsibility to keep your password confidential. If you are sharing a computer or are using a computer in a public area, you should log out before leaving our Web site in order to protect your information from other users. 

We are so sure that you will get valuable genealogy information and family history help with your World Vital Records subscription that we offer a 30 day money back guarantee. If at any time during your first 30 days of membership you do not get your money's worth simply call us on our toll free number at 1-888-377-0588 and request a refund. We will gladly refund your total membership amount. Simple as that! This money back guarantee applies to all World Vital Records membership plans and does not apply to any shipped products.

If the World Vital Records membership that you purchased included a product that was included as a premium or promotional offer (magazine subscriptions, software, eBooks, audio books, etc.) then the amount refunded will be reduced to cover the cost of the additional product. There are no refunds of magazine subscriptions, software, eBooks, audio books, or other downloads or shipped physical products in boxes. The sale of magazine subscriptions downloads, or other electronic, digital, or physical products are final. The amount refunded will be 50% of the purchase price to cover the cost of the World Vital Records membership.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit some pages of our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.  If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp).

**IF YOU ARE DISSATISFIED WITH ANY PORTION OF THIS AGREEMENT, DO NOT USE THE SERVICE.**

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our services. When we make changes to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of this Privacy Policy. Please review this Privacy Policy from time to time. If you are concerned about how we are protecting your information, please contact us at World Vital Records, Inc., 2975 Executive Parkway Ste 310, Lehi, Utah 84034, 84604, 888-377-0588.
